https://www.awardsideas.com/privacy-policy.html

Login Or Create An AccountYour Cart800.875.1725info@awardsideas.com
Left PanelCustom AwardsCrystal & Glass Awards Lucite & Acrylic Awards Deal Toys & Tombstones Stone Awards Metal Awards Recognition Walls Plaques Stock Awards
Quick Ship Awards
Acrylic & Lucite Awards
Eco-Friendly Awards
Crystal Awards
Glass Awards Art Glass AwardsJade AwardsStarphire Awards
Cultured Stone Awards
Marble & Granite Awards
Resin Cast Awards
Metal Cast / Machined Awards Aluminum AwardsStainless Steel AwardsZinc Alloy / Other Awards
Perpetual Awards
Wood Awards
Plaques Wood PlaquesMarble / Granite PlaquesCultured Stone PlaquesSlate PlaquesEco-Friendly Shadow Box Plaques
Business Card Awards
Donor Walls
Signage
Seals
Medallions & Coins
Corporate Jewelry Lapel PinsRingsPendantsBelt Buckles
Business Gifts BarwareDesk AccessoriesClocksPhoto FramesKey TagsBowls & Vases Certificate HoldersDrinkwareGolf giftsHoliday giftsTravel giftsRibbon awardsInformationDownload BrochureAbout usMonthly ContestNewsletter Sign UpBest PracticesReach Your GoalsAwards Ideas UniversityCustom Awards VideosArtworkCustomer Satisfaction FormCustomer TestimonialsFrequently Asked QuestionsOrdering AwardsSitemapShare Us
Home
>>
Privacy and PoliciesPrivacy PolicyWe implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All sensitive/credit information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our databases to be only accessed as stated above.
Awardsideas Companies Please visit our other website AwarenessIdeas.com Environmental employee awareness, motivation marketing solutions and materials.  My AccountLogin or create accountAccess your accountShopping cartNeed Help?Contact usFaqCompany InfoAbout UsSitemapGoogle SitemapNewsletter Sign upShipping PolicyPrivacy PolicyShare UsWe AcceptFlexi Promotional Marketing, Inc.2156 Maplehurst DriveCommerce, MI 48390TOLL-FREE: 800-875-1725
LOCAL: 248-987-6400 FAX: 248-987-6401Flexi Promotional Marketing, Inc.2156 Maplehurst DriveCommerce, MI 48390TOLL-FREE: 800-875-1725
LOCAL: 248-987-6400 FAX: 248-987-6401
Contact Us1 800-875-1725 or info@awardsideas.cominfo@flexidisplay.comWe're happy to brainstorm ideas with you. We'll create the perfect Award together!© AwardsIDEAS 2017. All Rights Reserved.
